hello everybody and welcome to part 7 of
大家好， 欢迎来到 第 7部分
our TV basics with Python tutorial
我们的电视基础与 Python 教程
series in this video we're going to be
在这个视频系列， 我们将 成为
talking about is getting mouse input
谈论得到鼠标输入
information actually when I say Mouse
实际上当我说 老鼠的时候
it's actually not just the mouse it's
它实际上不只是它的鼠标
any coordinate input so to speak so if
任何坐标输入都可以这么说
you have a phone and you're touching the
你有一个电话，你触摸了
phone this would include that kind of
电话这将包括 那种
input so again that's kind of the point
再次输入， 这是一个重点
of keavy is that we can have actually
keavy的是，我们 其实 可以有
multiple input to a device but anyways
多个输入到设备，但无论如何
that's what we're gonna cover now is how
这就是 我们现在要讲的是如何
to get you know what's where are the
让你知道那里是什么
coordinates that are being actually I
坐标实际上是我
don't know input or clicked or I don't
不知道输入或点击或我不知道
know what you would touched because
知道你会感动什么， 因为
that's literally what it's being called
这实际上就是它被称为的东西
as a touch so I guess that's probably
作为一个触摸，所以我想这可能是
the best thing to do so we're gonna be
最好的事情 是这样做 ，我们会成为的
touching stuff okay so now this is where
触摸东西 好，所以现在这是 在哪里
we left off we had this nice little
我们离开了，我们有这么好的一点
application that's cool
很酷的应用程序
we could work with that a little bit
我们可以与 一点点工作
more later in buttons and all that but
更晚些时候在按钮和所有那些，但
for now we're going to again kind of
现在我们要 重新种
break this down to a really simple
把它分解成一个非常简单的东西
element so you can see at the most basic
元素，所以你可以看到最基本的
level what's involved in getting a mouse
级别 是什么在获得鼠标
you know input or a finger input or
你知道输入或手指输入或
whatever so uh we're going to delete
无论如何，我们要删除
this we don't really actually delete
这我们并没有真正 删除
that I'm gonna just rename it basically
我会基本上重新命名它
but from kvu Y X dot widget now we're
但从 kvu YX点小部件 现在我们
going to import just widget again we'll
我们将再次导入小部件
use that for now and now we need a new
现在使用， 现在我们需要一个新的
class so we're going to say class uh
所以我们要说班级呃
we're going to call this class touch
我们打算称这类 触摸
touch input and it's just going to
触摸输入，它只是要
inherit from widget and then we'll do :
从小部件继承，然后我们将执行：
and now we're going to define def um on
现在我们要 定义高清庵上
underscore touch underscore down and
下划线触摸下划线和
then self just for typical standards
然后自己只是为了典型的标准
there and then touch ok so then : now
然后触摸OK，然后：现在
let's just print the touch now this on
让我们现在就打印触摸这个
touch down is key V code okay so bring
触摸下来是关键的V代码可以 带来
this up and over so here we go input
这一遍又一遍，所以在这里我们去输入
management okay so if you go to kiva.org
管理好， 所以如果你去kiva.org
then go to docs guide
然后去文档 指南
and we come down to input management
我们回到 输入管理
here you can see these are basically all
在这里你可以看到这些基本上都是
of the things that you have at your
的， 你必须在 你的 事
disposal on touch down on touch move on
一触即发处理
touch up which basically means a release
触摸这基本上意味着释放
right so you can hold your mouse key
所以你可以拿着你的鼠标键
down and then you can you know let it go
下来，然后你可以知道 放手
so you've got those or you can you know
所以你有这些，或者你可以知道
touch the screen and stop touching the
触摸屏幕 并停止触摸 屏幕
screen and so on anyway this on touch
屏幕等无论如何这接触
down for example is a kind of like part
例如下来是一种 相似的部分
of you know TV almost so anyway on touch
你无论如何都会接触到 电视
down self touch moving over what we're
向下移动我们的自我
going to do now is we're just printing
现在要做的是我们只是在印刷
the touch so that's easy enough
触摸很容易
instead of having simple TV for return
而不是有简单的电视回报
float layout however we're going to have
浮动布局但是我们将 不得不
it return touch input and that should
它返回 触摸输入，应该
really be it as far as adding touch
真的是它只要添加触摸
input is concerned now we should see it
现在我们应该看到投入
printed out to our console so here is
打印到我们的控制台，所以这里
our TV application here is our console
我们的电视应用程序是我们的控制台
let's make some clicks okay so as you
让我们点击 一下就可以了
can see as we click we get various
可以 看到，当我们点击我们得到各种
elements here for the position okay
元素在这里的位置没关系
and so let's click write right here for
所以让我们点击 这里写
example so if we click right here we get
例如，如果我们点击这里，我们会得到
a couple of things right we get
我们得到 的一些 事情
basically the you wear it so here and
基本上你 在这里 穿着它
then let's click see this would be zeros
然后让我们点击看到这将是零
here let's click here okay so I remember
这里让我们点击 这里好， 所以我记得
what I was talking about before with
我 之前 在谈论什么
using X&Y and zero is nothingness and
使用X＆Y 和零是没有和
one is fullness so as you can see we
一个是丰满的， 所以你 可以 看到我们
clicked right at the bottom left corner
点击左下角的右侧
and pretty close to zero elements then
然后非常接近零元素
we click kind of towards the top right
我们点击右上角的种类
there almost a 1:1 so you get that
几乎 有 1：1，所以你明白了
information plus you get the actual X&Y
信息 加上你得到了实际的 X＆Y
coordinate information so this is a
坐标信息， 所以这是一个
little more relative so if you're
如果你是这样的话，多一点亲戚
expecting that you're going to be using
期待你将会使用
a lot of different sizes and you want
很多 不同的尺寸 和你想要的
more of the relative because you might
更多的亲戚， 因为你可能
be using a float layout for example this
例如使用浮动布局
might be the superior method to use
可能是最好的使用方法
because position might change and then
因为职位可能会改变，然后
you would have to input all kind I don't
你将不得不输入所有我不喜欢的东西
know some sort of algorithm to calculate
知道某种计算算法
what are the new dimensions or where
什么是新维度或哪里
might the new I don't know think that
可能新的我不知道以为
the person's
这个人的
possibly clicking B&R we closed a lot of
可能点击B＆R 我们 关闭了很多
it is a lot of what goes on in game
这是很多游戏 中 发生的 事情
development GUI development is where is
开发GUI开发是在哪里
the user clicking and are they actually
用户点击并且实际上是他们
clicking on something or especially in a
点击某物或特别是在某物中
game has there been a collision or have
游戏已经发生过碰撞 或拥有
we actually shot the person or whatever
我们实际上射击了这个 人或 其他什么
so it for it to have this is actually
所以它 实际上是这样的
quite nice because it's more of a
相当不错， 因为它更像 是一个
relative positioning not an actual hard
相对定位不是一个实际的困难
static-x and why anyway that's that I'm
static-x 和 为什么无论如何 这就是我
actually gonna like well IIM fitting the
实际上我会喜欢 IIM 适合的
other one too so so another thing that
其他人也是如此， 以至于另一件事
you might want to have is you might want
你可能 想要的是你可能想要的
to have just general Mouse position but
只有一般的鼠标位置， 但
a probably not and and also the reason
一个可能不是， 也是原因
why that's not really useful for keavy
为什么这对 keavy来说 不是很有用
is the idea of key v is to be um a you
关键 v的想法是成为你
know all kinds of applications so in
知道各种应用程序，以便在
theory 8 with kv to work on a phone you
理论8 与 KV 在你的手机上工作
can't really have a mouse like just
不能像真正的鼠标一样
general mouse position on a phone like
一般的鼠标在手机上的位置
the only way you would possibly do that
唯一的方法是你可能会这样做
is by using your phone and like in
是使用 您的手机， 喜欢
touchdown and then move right otherwise
达阵，然后 向右 移动， 否则
you can't move a mouse so the same thing
你不能移动鼠标于是同样的 事情
is true over here so the only so the
在这里是真的， 所以唯一如此
next thing you would really want to
接下来的事情你真的想要
track is after a touchdown where is the
轨道是一个接地后哪里是
movement and then obviously you would
运动，然后显然你 会
want to track maybe a touch up movement
想跟踪可能 的触摸动作
so for example let's um let's just close
例如，让我们来关闭吧
out of this and so we've got on touch
出于这一点， 所以我们已经接触了
down now we can do define on underscore
现在我们可以定义下划线
touch underscore move again it's just
触摸下划线再次移动它只是
self touch polling print touch okay so
自我触摸轮询打印触摸 没关系 等等
basically the same parameters and then I
基本上和我一样的参数
believe the other one is just touch up
相信另一个人只是摸起来
so I was going to go ahead and just add
所以我要继续 前进并添加
that one as well on touch up right so
那个人也是这么做的
then let's go ahead let's just copy this
那么让我们继续 吧，我们只是复制这个
because it's basically all the same so
因为它基本上都是一样的 ，所以
copy paste on touch move now on touch up
触摸复制粘贴现在进入 润色
and print let's just add here at least
并打印至少在这里添加
oh okay save and run that real quick
哦好吧保存并快速运行
okay so now let me move this down so you
好吧，现在让 我 把这个 下来，让你
can see it whizzing by and so we're
可以看到它呼啸而过，所以我们
holding the mouse now and we're moving
现在拿着鼠标，我们正在移动
around we can see all those elements and
我们可以看到 所有这些元素 和
then we release and sure enough we got
然后我们释放 并确信我们得到了
our released message so this is where
我们发布的消息，所以这是在哪里
the mouse was released in the
鼠标被释放
coordinates and then again the general
坐标，然后再一般
relative I don't know trying to think of
亲戚我不知道在想什么
a better better word for it but anyway
无论如何 ， 这是一个更好的词
but yeah so that was where I was raised
但是， 是的， 那是我被抚养的地方
in terms of 0 & 1 so I suppose for
在0 和 1方面， 所以我想
relative or normalized maybe I think of
相对的或正常化的，也许我想到了
a good word for it anyway so that's how
无论如何，这是一个好消息，所以就是这样
you get like Mouse events and stuff like
你得到像鼠标事件和类似的东西
that and so from here we can actually do
从这里开始，我们 实际上可以做到
quite a few cool stuff and I think my
相当多的 很酷的东西，我想 我的
favorite example has always been the
最喜欢的例子一直是
paint application and because it kind of
油漆应用程序，因为它的一种
shows off the canvas ability of keavy so
这样就展现了keavy的画布能力
keavy has a pretty cool canvas ability
凯维有一个非常酷的画布能力
and we can actually draw on the canvas
我们其实可以在画布上 绘制
with our mouse and since we now have
与我们的鼠标，因为我们现在有
what's required to track when the mouse
跟踪鼠标时需要什么
is pressed when the mouse moves and
当鼠标 移动 时 按下
where that mouse moves like literally
鼠标 像字面意思那样移动
every movement is being tracked here
每个动作都在这里跟踪
where the mouse moves and then when it's
鼠标在哪里移动，然后是何时移动
done moving we have all that so moving
我们已经完成了 所有这些动作
and creating some sort of paint
并创建某种油漆
application or somewhere where we can
应用程序或我们可以的地方
actually draw like you know hi okay
实际上就像你知道的那样画你好
should be relatively simple from here
应该是从 这里 相对简单
right so anyways that's what we're going
右 所以反正这就是 我们接下来要做的事情
to be moving on to in the next video is
要继续 在下一个视频是
just creating like a simple application
只是创建 一个简单的应用程序
where we can draw stuff to the actual
我们 可以在这里真实地绘制东西
screen so stay tuned for that if you
如果你愿意的话， 敬请关注
guys have any questions or comments on
你们有任何问题或意见
this video please feel free to leave
此视频请随时离开
them below otherwise as always thanks
他们在下面，否则一如既往的感谢
for watching thanks for all the support
观看感谢 所有支持
subscriptions until next time
订阅直到下一次